PRASETYO **DENNY** WIBOWO

2621 S Lawrence St., Philadelphia, PA 19148 | Cell: (267)-902-9942 | Email: indocoffee@gmail.com

PROFILE:

Advanced web developer with 8 plus years of experience in developing website from the ground up. Extensive knowledge in PHP based CMS, including creating custom templates for both Wordpress and Joomla. Experienced in PHP framework such as Laravel and Codeigniter. Ability to manage multiple projects, and communicating with the client directly. Experienced in Javascript native, and frameworks such as Reactjs and AngularJS.

QUALIFICATIONS:

Web Development Core:

PHP, JavaScript, ReactJS, AngularJS, Jquery, HTML, CSS, Less, SaSS

PHP frameworks:

Laravel, Codelgniter, Symfony

CMS and E-commerce:

Joomla, Wordpress, Drupal, Shopify, X-Cart

Database Administration/DBMS:

Mariadb, MySQL, PostGRE, MS SQL, Oracle, SQLite

Other:

Git, Bootstrap, LAMP, WAMP, Apache2, nginx, VPS, IIS, Cpanel, WHM

EDUCATION:

Bachelor degree in Computer Science, Sekolah Tinggi Teknik Surabaya, Indonesia 2005

WORK HISTORY:

2015- current Website Developer, Lyquix.

2007-2015 Website Developer and Project Manager, B2B Design Development, LLC.

• 2006-2007 Freelance coder and web developer.

• 2005-2006 **IT Division Manager**, Pt. Drupadi Agung Lestari.

COMPETENCIES:

- Strong Analytical and problem-solving skills
- A fast learner and a hard worker
- Ability to perform under pressure, both individually and collectively

PORTFOLIO:

• www.pwibowo.xyz/#myWork